Mary Seaman Collection of Arlington Mills Christmas Party Photographs 6771 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mary Seaman Collection of Arlington Mills Christmas Party Photographs
1946
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mary Seaman
Arlington Mills
American Textile History Museum
6771 P
1 folders
1 file folder
Gelatin silver print, photographs.
Photographs of the 1946 Christmas Party at Arlington Mills in Lawrence, Massachusetts.
10062548
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, October 06, 2017
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, November 30, 2017
Scope and Contents
Inccludes en snapshots of a Christmas Party at Arlington Mills, in Lawrence, Massachusetts. This party most likely took place in 1946. Pictured are groups of employees, Santa Claus, Christmas decorations, and mill machinery.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6517: Arlington Mills Records 6517 G: Arlington Mills Graphics 6517 GPN: Arlington Mills Glass Plate Negatives 6517 P: Arlington Mills Photographs 6517 PUBS: Arlington Mills Publications
Custodial History
American Textile History Museum Collection, gift of Mary Seaman
Christmas party; Employees; Spinning machinery; Textile machinery; Textile workers; Lawrence (Mass.); Santa Claus; American Textile History Museum
10062548
- Female employees at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.1, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several female employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. They are sitting at a table on which are several bottles of what appears to be wine or champagne. "Merry Xmas" sign on pole in background.
- Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.2, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., seated at a table with Santa Claus in the background at a Christmas party, probably in 1946.
- Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.3, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., in a group portrait with Santa Claus seated in the center. Tinsel hangs between poles in the background; Christmas party.
- Female employees at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.4, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a group of female employees posed together at a Christmas party, in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass. One woman holds a 'Merry Xmas" sign; two others hold a partially obscured sign that reads, in part, "Holiday..."
- Male employee with Santa Claus at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.5, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Male employee with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a male employee of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., with Santa Claus at a Christmas party. Tinsel hangs in the background.
- Female employees at table at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.6, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Female employees at table at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several female employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a table at a Christmas party. The table is loaded with plates of food and cups.
- Christmas party, spinning room, ATHM# 1988.135.7, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Christmas party, spinning room, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a table in the spinning room of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a Christmas party. Several female employees are sitting at the table; one male and two female employees stand behind it. Creels and spinning machinery visible in background.
- Santa Claus at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.8, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts Santa Claus at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass. The backs of several employees are visible on the right. tinsel is strung between two poles.
- Santa Claus with male employee at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.9, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Santa Claus with male employee at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts Santa Claus seated on the knee of a male employee at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass. Creels and spinning machinery visible in background.
- Female employees at Christmas party, ATHM# 1988.135.10, 1946; black and white photograph; 9 x 9 cm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a group of female employees posed together at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass.